[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tag belongs to what 1973 movie?  \nWhere robot men and women are programmed to serve you for... Romance... Violence... Anything.", "correct_answer": "Westworld", "incorrect_answers": ["Blade Runner", "I, Robot", "Futureworld"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Andy say was pretty gross in the movie The Breakfast Club?", "correct_answer": "Claire dehydrating", "incorrect_answers": ["Benders feet", "Allisons hand-eating", "Brian crying"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Dodgeball, American cyclist Lance Armstrong made a cameo appearance giving Peter La Fleur a pep talk.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the classic movie Jaws come out in the movie theatres?", "correct_answer": "1975", "incorrect_answers": ["1973", "1979", "1971"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the human body are the Wormian bones, named after Ole Worm, located?", "correct_answer": "Cranium", "incorrect_answers": ["Thorax", "Mandible", "Pelvis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the butlers name in the movie Wedding Crashers?", "correct_answer": "Randolph", "incorrect_answers": ["Howard", "Carlton", "Jeffrey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which month is United States Aquarium Month, Candy Month, Dairy Month and Turkey Lovers Month?", "correct_answer": "June", "incorrect_answers": ["November", "August", "October"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a breed of dog?", "correct_answer": "Ferret terrier", "incorrect_answers": ["Pom-a-poo", "Lakeland terrier", "Fox terrier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which book is this quote: When Gregor Samsa awoke he was transformed into an incredibly large, disgusting vermin.?", "correct_answer": "Kafkas The Metamorphosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Kerouacs On the Road", "Dostoevsky s Crime and Punishment", "Goethes Faustus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "References to measurements of a circular basin in the Bible (Kings 7:23), appears to give what corresponding value for pi?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2.71828", "22/7", "3.14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the water soluble pigments that give wine its red color?", "correct_answer": "anthocyanins", "incorrect_answers": ["ionons", "damascones", "phycobilins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the basic unit of electric pressure, also known as emf?", "correct_answer": "Volt", "incorrect_answers": ["Current", "Amp", "Watt"]}]